export default questions = [
	{
		title: "D",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question:
					"What term which originally referred to non-analog signals now often refers to anything virtual or internet-based?",
				answer: "Digital",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question:
					"What computer company sells products such as the Inspiron, Latitude, and OptiPlex?",
				answer: "Dell",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question:
					"What social platform, primarily associated with gaming, provides messaging, voice chat, and video call functionality?",
				answer: "Discord",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question:
					"Which type of electrical current provides mostly constant one-directional electric charge?",
				answer: "Direct Current (DC)",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question:
					"What term, often associated with CSV files, refers to characters that specify the boundary between different pieces of data?",
				answer: "Delimeter",
			},
		],
	},
	{
		title: "E",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question:
					"What is the name of the major spreadsheet software developed by Microsoft?",
				answer: "Excel",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question:
					"Electricity is caused by the flow of many of what type of sub-atomic particle?",
				answer: "Electron",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question:
					"What is the process of using algorithms to hide data so that it can be securely transferred?",
				answer: "Encryption",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question:
					"What kind of technology is used to connect Local-Area Networks via cables?",
				answer: "Ethernet",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question:
					"What datatype in C++ and related languages uses values that represent a finite set of constants?",
				answer: "Enum (enumeration)",
			},
		],
	},
	{
		title: "B",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question:
					"What wireless technology uses radio waves to transfer data to paired devices within 33ft of the device?",
				answer: "Bluetooth",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question:
					"What is the term for forms of identification such as fingerprinting that are based on distinct physiological characteristics?",
				answer: "Biometrics",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question:
					"What term refers to either preinstalled unwanted software that takes up space or software that slows down a machine with ineficciency?",
				answer: "Bloatware",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question:
					"Usually measured in hertz, what term refers to the maximum rate of data transfer in a network?",
				answer: "Bandwidth",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question:
					'Sometimes called a "data highway", what term refers to pathways of data transfer, typically connected to the CPU?',
				answer: "Bus",
			},
		],
	},
	{
		title: "U",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question:
					"What is the process of transfering data from one system to a larger system, usually the internet?",
				answer: "Uploading",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question: "What is the technical term for a website's address?",
				answer: "Uniform Resource Locator (URL)",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question:
					"What game engine associated with indie games creates 2D and 3D games and competes with the Unreal Engine?",
				answer: "Unity",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question:
					"What common standard for text representation can represent more symbols than ASCII?",
				answer: "Unicode",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question:
					"What device is used to provide constant battery power to a device in the event of a disruption?",
				answer: "Uninterruptable Power Supply (UPS)",
			},
		],
	},
	{
		title: "G",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question:
					"What technology company started as a major search engine and now makes phones, a web browser, and applications of all kinds?",
				answer: "Google",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question:
					"What is the unit for a frequency of a billion cycles per second?",
				answer: "Gigahertz",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question:
					"In electronics, what term refers to either a voltage reference point or the place that electricity drains into?",
				answer: "Ground",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question:
					"What platform is used by software developers to collaborate and manage versions of code?",
				answer: "GitHub",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question:
					"What four-letter acronym refers to the concept that the quality of an operation's results depend on the quality of its inputs?",
				answer: "GIGO (Garbage In, Garbage Out)",
			},
		],
	},
];
